Guide to the Wells Rich Greene Inc. Records, 1954-1998 and undated RL.01365
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Wells Rich Greene Inc. records
1954-1998 and undated
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Wells Rich Greene, Inc.
RL.01365
250 Linear Feet
The Wells Rich Greene, Inc. (WRG) advertising agency was founded in 1966 by Mary Wells, Richard Rich, and Stewart Greene, who were associates at Jack Tinker and Partners agency. Until its demise in 1998, WRG was ranked as one of the top 15 advertising agencies in the United States. The Wells Rich Greene, Inc. (WRG) Records contain primarily print advertisements and broadcast commercials and advertising spots for clients of WRG. Materials span 1966-1998 and include magazine and newspaper advertisements, proof sheets, audiocassettes, videocassettes, analog and digital audio tape. Corporate documentation includes press releases, clipping files, and staff photographs and slides. Clients represented in the collection include: American Motors; Bristol-Myers (Boost, Clairol, Herbal Essence, Vagistat); Cadbury (Canada Dry, Schweppes); Continental Airlines; Ford; IBM; ITT (Technology Institute, Sheraton); Liberty Mutual; MCI; Miles Laboratories (Alka-Seltzer); New York Department of Commerce; Pan Am; Philip Morris (Benson & Hedges, Player, Dunhill); Procter & Gamble (Gain, Oil of Olay, Pringles, Folder's, Sure); Ralston Purina (Chex, Dog Chow, Tender Vittles); Seagram; TWA; and Warnaco (Warner's lingerie). Acquired as part of the John W. Hartman Center for Sales, Advertising & Marketing History.
7500 Items
Access Restrictions
Collection is open for research.
Researchers must register and agree to copyright and privacy laws before using this collection.
In addition, original audiovisual materials are closed to patron use. Technical Services staff need to produce use copies before contents can be accessed.
All or portions of this collection may be housed off-site in Duke University's Library Service Center. The library may require up to 48 hours to retrieve these materials for research use.
Please contact Research Services staff before visiting the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library to use this collection.
Provenance
The Wells Rich Greene Inc. Records were received by the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library as a gift in 1998.
Biographical and Historical Note
1966 Opened upon the departures of Mary Wells, Richard Rich, and Stewart Greene from Jack Tinker and Partners
1967 Won American Motors Company (AMC) account
1968 Won Trans World Airlines (TWA) account Initial public offering
1969 Richard Rich left WRG
1970 AMC Gremlin launch Won Alka-Seltzer account (Miles Laboratories)
1971 Agency of record, Procter & Gamble
1974 WRG reverted to private ownership Stewart Greene left WRG
1979 Won Ford Motor Company corporate account
1990 Mary Wells Lawrence resigned as CEO, replaced by Ken Olshan
1991 Majority stake sold to BDDP; renamed Wells Rich Greene BDDP
1996 Sold to GGT PLC (London)
1997 Renamed Wells BDDP; soon after sold to Omnicom Group
1998 Dissolved by Omnicom
Among the notable campaign slogans created by WRG: Plop, plop, fizz, fizz, I can't believe I ate the whole thing, and Try it, you'll like it (all for Alka-Seltzer); I (heart) New York (New York State Commerce Commission); Trust the Midas Touch (Midas Muffler); At Ford, Quality is Job 1 (Ford Motor Company); and Raise Your Hand If You're Sure (Procter & Gamble's Sure anti-perpirant).
1928 May 25 Born Mary Georgene Berg, Youngstown, Oh.
Circa 1945 Attended Neighborhood Playhouse School of the Theater, New York, N.Y.
Circa 1947 Attended Carnegie Institute of Technology Married Bert Wells
1951 Advertising writer, McKelvey's Department Store, Youngstown, Oh.
1952 Fashion Advertising Manager, Macy's Department Store, New York, N.Y.
1953 Copy Chief, McCann-Erickson agency
1957-1963 Worked at Doyle Dane Bernbach
1964-1966 Worked at Jack Tinker and Partners; primary responsibility for Braniff Airlines account
1965 Divorced Bert Wells
1966 Opened Wells Rich Greene, Inc. with Richard Rich, and Stewart Greene, associates from Jack Tinker and Partners
1967 Married Harding Lawrence, CEO of Braniff Airlines
1968 Upon WRG Initial public offering, became first woman CEO of a company listed on the New York Stock Exchange
1969 Considered the highest-paid woman in U.S. advertising industry Inducted into Copywriters' Hall of Fame
1970 Honorary Doctor of Law, Babson College
1971 Named Advertising Woman of the Year Honorary Doctorate, Carnegie-Mellon University
2002 Memoir, A Big Life in Advertising, published Harding Lawrence died
Sources: Advertising Age Encyclopedia of Advertising (Fitzroy Dearborn 2003); The Ad Men and Women (Applegate 1994); Who's Who in Advertising (1963-); Wikipedia, Mary Wells Lawrence
Collection Overview
The Wells Rich Greene, Inc. (WRG) Records contain primarily print advertisements and broadcast commercials and advertising spots for clients of WRG. Materials span 1966-1998 and include magazine and newspaper advertisements, proof sheets, audiocassettes, videocassettes, analog and digital audio tape. Corporate documentation includes press releases, clipping files, and staff photographs and slides. Clients represented in the collection include: American Motors; Bristol-Myers (Boost, Clairol, Herbal Essence, Vagistat); Cadbury (Canada Dry, Schweppes); Continental Airlines; Ford; IBM; ITT (Technology Institute, Sheraton); Liberty Mutual; MCI; Miles Laboratories (Alka-Seltzer); New York Department of Commerce; Pan Am; Philip Morris (Benson & Hedges, Player, Dunhill); Procter & Gamble (Gain, Oil of Olay, Pringles, Folder's, Sure); Ralston Purina (Chex, Dog Chow, Tender Vittles); Seagram; TWA; and Warnaco (Warner's lingerie).
NOTE: Throughout this finding aid, TRT refers to Total Running Time, the total duration of content contained on a tape or film.
Collection Arrangement
Collection is arranged into two Series: Print Advertisements and Documentation; and Audiovisual Materials.
Related Material
Related materials may be found in the following collections held in the Hartman Center for Sales, Advertising & Marketing History:
Bates Worldwide, Inc. Records
D'Arcy Masius Benton & Bowles Archives
J. Walter Thompson Company. Domestic Advertisements Collection
Warwick Baker O'Neill Records
Digital audio tapes; Clippings (information artifacts); Photographs; Audiotapes; Advertising agencies; Advertising agencies -- United States; Television commercials -- United States; Videocassettes; Audiocassettes; Advertising agencies -- United States -- History; Television advertising -- United States; Proofs (printed matter); Slides (photographs); Philip Morris Incorporated; Pan American World Airways, Inc.; Ralston Purina Company; Procter & Gamble Company; Trans World Airlines; Seagram Company; Wells Rich Greene, Inc.; Warnaco (Firm); American Motors Corporation; Bristol-Myers Company; Cadbury Beverages, Inc.; Continental Airlines; Ford Motor Company; International Business Machines Corporation; ITT Corporation; John W. Hartman Center for Sales, Advertising & Marketing History; Lawrence, Mary Wells; Liberty Mutual Insurance Company; MCI Communications Corporation; Miles Laboratories; New York. Department of Commerce
- Print Advertisements and Documentation, 1966-1998 and undated (Acc. 98-0290), 104 boxes
  - Advertisements, 1966-1994 and undated
    - Small Boxes
      - Amaretto, 1976-1979 (Box 1)
      - American Motors, 1969-1972 (Box 1)
      - American Motors (continued), 1969-1972 (Box 2)
      - BIC, 1972-1982 (Box 3)
      - Bonanza, 1972-1974 and undated (Box 3)
      - Caron, undated (Box 3)
      - Citibank, 1973-1980 (Box 3)
      - Citizen Watches, 1980-1982 (Box 4)
      - Columbia Minerva (CM), 1976-1977 (Box 4)
      - Continental Airlines, 1990 (Box 4)
      - Continental Airlines (continued), 1990-1991 (Box 5)
      - Continental Baking, 1985 (Box 6)
      - Diner's Club, 1979-1981 (Box 6)
      - Dolfi, 1978-1979 (Box 6)
      - Ford, 1979-1981 (Box 6)
      - Ford--Non-automotive, 1980 (Box 7)
      - The Gap, 1984 (Box 7)
      - General Mills, 1968-1975 (Box 7)
      - Hertz (Japan), 1991 (Box 8)
      - Hush Puppies, 1973-1978 (Box 8)
      - Hush Puppies (continued), 1978-1986 (Box 9)
      - Junior Achievement, undated (Box 9)
      - Lancel, 1979-1980 (Box 9)
      - Loehmann's, 1991-1992 (Box 9)
      - MCI, 1984-1988 (Box 10)
      - MCI (continued), 1988-1989 (Box 11)
      - MCI (continued), 1988-1990 (Box 12)
      - MCI (continued), 1990 (Box 13)
      - Midas, 1972-1985 (Box 14)
      - Midas (continued), 1975-1977 (Box 15)
      - Midas (continued), 1978-1980 (Box 16)
      - Miles Labs, 1971-1982 (Box 16)
      - Mobil Land Communities (mounted presentations), undated (Box 16)
      - Mobil Oil, 1985-1990 (Box 17)
      - Multiple Sclerosis, 1975-1977 (Box 17)
      - National Enquirer, 1986 and undated (Box 17)
      - National Geographic, 1977-1983 (Box 17)
      - National Kidney Foundation, 1968 and undated (Box 17)
      - New York State (Lottery), 1973-1984 (Box 18)
      - New York State (Lottery) (continued), 1977-1984 (Box 19)
      - New York State (Business development), 1978-1982 (Box 19)
      - New York State (continued), 1979-1984 (Box 20)
      - New York State (continued), 1984-1988 (Box 21)
      - New York State (includes advertisements for business development), 1987-1991 (Box 22)
      - Olympus, 1979 (Box 23)
      - Paine Webber, 1973-1975 (Box 23)
      - Pan Am, 1982 (Box 24)
      - Pan Am (continued), 1983 (Box 25)
      - Pan Am (continued), 1983-1984 (Box 26)
      - Pan Am (continued), 1984 (Box 27)
      - Pan Am (continued), 1984 (Box 28)
      - Pan Am (continued), 1984-1985 (Box 29)
      - Pan Am (continued), 1985 (Box 30)
      - Pan Am (continued), 1985-1986 (Box 31)
      - Pan Am (continued), 1986 (Box 32)
      - Pan Am (continued), 1986 (Box 33)
      - Pan Am (continued), 1986 (Box 34)
      - Pan Am (continued), 1987-1988 (Box 35)
      - Pan Am (Shuttle), 1988 (Box 35)
      - Passport Scotch, undated (Box 35)
      - Philip Morris (Box 36)
        - Benson & Hedges (continued), 1972-1975 (Box 36)
        - Benson & Hedges (continued), 1973-1975 (Box 37)
        - Benson & Hedges (continued), 1975-1979 (Box 38)
        - Benson & Hedges (continued), 1977-1986 (Box 39)
        - Benson & Hedges (continued), 1980-1985 (Box 40)
        - Benson & Hedges (continued), 1982-1986 (Box 41)
        - Benson & Hedges (continued), 1985-1989 (Box 42)
        - Benson & Hedges (continued), 1986-1990 (Box 43)
        - Benson & Hedges (continued), 1987-1990 (Box 44)
        - Benson & Hedges mounted presentations, undated (Box 45)
        - Dunhill cigarettes, 1985-1986 (Box 46)
        - Flavor Tree snack foods, 1968 (Box 46)
        - Players cigarettes, 1983-1984 (Box 46)
        - Raffles cigarettes, 1983 (Box 46)
        - RIO cigarettes, 1985 (Box 46)
      - Procter & Gamble, 1966-1981 (Box 47)
      - PBS (Public Broadcasting Service), 1970-1971 (Box 48)
      - Purolator, 1983-1985 (Box 48)
      - Ralston Purina (Box 49)
        - General, 1970-1976 (Box 49)
        - Dog Chow, Chex, 1972-1976 (Box 49)
        - Tender Vittles, Cat Chow, 1972-1976 (Box 50)
        - Other products, 1977-1988 (Box 50)
      - Royal Crown Cola (RC Cola, Diet Rite, Gatorade), 1969-1970 (Box 51)
      - Samsonite, 1969-1970 (Box 51)
      - Savin, 1978-1984 (Box 52)
      - Seagram's, 1970-1971 (Box 52)
      - Standard Brands (Chase & Sanborn, Fleischmann's), 1978-1980 (Box 52)
      - SUNOCO, 1977-1985 (Box 53)
      - Tic Tac, 1977 (Box 53)
      - TWA, 1968 (Box 54)
      - TWA (continued), 1968 (Box 55)
      - TWA (continued), 1968 (Box 56)
      - TWA (continued), 1970s (Box 57)
      - TWA (continued), 1974 (Box 58)
      - TWA (Southeast Asia), 1976 (Box 58)
      - Union, 1978 (Box 58)
      - Vivaria, 1973 (Box 58)
      - Waring, 1977-1978 (Box 58)
      - Warnaco/ Warner's, 1974-1977 (Box 59)
      - Warnaco/ Warner's (continued), 1977-1978 (Box 60)
      - Warnaco/ Warner's (continued), 1979-1981 (Box 61)
      - Warnaco/ Warner's (continued), 1983-1991 (Box 62)
      - Wedgewood, 1988-1989 (Box 62)
      - Westinghouse, 1973-1977 (Box 62)
      - Wells Rich and Greene Inc., 1968-1976 (Box 63)
      - Wells Rich and Greene Inc. (continued), 1973-1990 (Box 64)
      - Wells Rich and Greene Inc. (continued), 1990 (Box 65)
    - Large Boxes
      - Amaretto, 1977-1978 (Box 66)
      - American Motors, 1967-1969 (Box 66)
      - Atari, 1983 (Box 66)
      - Braniff Airlines, 1979 (Box 67)
      - Brown-Vinters, 1968 (Box 67)
      - Cadbury, 1987-1988 (Box 67)
      - Chase Bank, 1982-1984 (Box 67)
      - Chase Bank (continued), 1984-1985 (Box 68)
      - Cosmopolitan Magazine, 1987-1988 (Box 68)
      - Diner's Club, 1980 (Box 68)
      - Marshall Fields, 1983-1985 (Box 68)
      - Ford, 1983-1987 (Box 68)
      - Halston, 1978-1980 (Box 69)
      - Halston, Max Factor and Fieldcrest (mixed clients), 1978-1980 (Box 69)
      - Hunt-Wesson Foods, 1969- (Box 69)
      - IBM, 1989-1992 (Box 70)
      - IBM (continued), 1991-1994 (Box 71)
      - IBM--Guidelines, undated (Box 72)
      - IBM--Presentation, undated (Box 73)
      - IBM (mounted presentations loose on shelf), undated (Box 74)
      - JC Penney, 1979 (Box 75)
      - La Rosa, undated (Box 75)
      - Love Cosmetics, 1969-1975 (Box 75)
      - Max Factor, 1978-1985 (Box 76)
      - Mobil Land Communities (mounted presentations), undated (Box 77)
      - National Geographic, 1971-1981 (Box 78)
      - New York State (business development), 1979 (Box 78)
      - Olympus, 1979-1980 (Box 78)
      - Pan Am, 1982 (Box 79)
      - Pan Am (continued), 1982-1983 (Box 80)
      - Pan Am (continued), 1983 (Box 81)
      - Pan Am Express, 1988 (Box 81)
      - Passport Scotch, 1969-1972 (Box 82)
      - Personna, 1966-1969 (Box 82)
      - Philip Morris (Box 83)
        - Benson & Hedges, 1960s-1983 (Box 83)
        - Players cigarettes, undated (Box 84)
        - Raffles cigarettes, undated (Box 84)
      - Procter & Gamble, 1981-1987 (Box 85)
      - Rainier Beer, 1967-1968 (Box 86)
      - Ralph Lauren, 1987-1988 (Box 86)
      - Ralston Purina (mostly Chex), 1972-1979 (Box 86)
      - SUNOCO, 1976-1977 (Box 86)
      - TWA (advertisements by former agency), 1968 (Box 86)
      - TWA (Canadian Air), 1969 (Box 87)
      - TWA (trade advertisements), 1969 (Box 87)
      - Utica Club beer, 1968 (Box 88)
      - Warnaco, 1986-1990 (Box 88)
      - Warren, 1990-1991 (Box 88)
      - Western Union, 1967-1969 (Box 88)
      - Westinghouse, 1974-1975 (Box 88)
      - Wells Rich and Greene Inc. advertising scrapbook (including competitors' advertisements), undated (Box 89)
  - Corporate Documentation, 1966-1998 and undated
    - General (Box 90)
      - General files, undated (Box 90)
      - Ad Agency Reputations, 1996 (Box 90)
      - BDDP financial notebook, undated (Box 90)
      - BDDP Network chronological notebook, 1994-1996 (Box 90)
      - Company promotions, undated (Box 90)
      - Employee resumes, undated (Box 90)
      - Frank Assuma speech, 1997 (Box 90)
      - Mary Wells files, 1970-1974 (Box 91)
      - Move Book, undated (Box 91)
      - WRG Brands, 1995-1997 (Box 91)
      - WRG thirtieth anniversary, circa 1996 (Box 91)
      - Photographic Materials
        - Office candid photos, undated (Box 91)
        - Proof sheets, undated (Box 91)
        - Staff photographs, undated
          - General photographs, undated (Box 91)
          - General slides, undated (Box 91)
          - Frank Assuma, Chairman, CEO, undated (Box 92)
          - Douglas Atkin, EVP and Strategic Planning Director, undated (Box 92)
          - Lynn Blumenfield, undated (Box 92)
          - Steve Davis, CEO, undated (Box 92)
          - Paula Forman, President, undated (Box 92)
          - Paula Forman and Douglas Atkin, undated (Box 92)
          - Adelaide Horton, Chief Operating Officer, undated (Box 92)
          - Linda Kaplan Thaler, Creative Director, undated (Box 92)
    - Clippings (Box 93)
      - 1966-1970, General (Box 93)
      - 1967, Mary Wells clippings (Box 93)
    - Clippings (continued) (Box 94)
      - 1986-1991, General (Box 94)
      - 1990, Merger press (Box 94)
      - 1990, Miscellaneous press (Box 94)
    - Clippings (continued) (Box 95)
      - 1990-1991, General (Box 95)
    - Clippings (continued) (Box 96)
      - 1992-1993, General (Box 96)
    - Clippings (continued) (Box 97)
      - 1993-1994, General (Box 97)
      - 1993-1994, Disruption articles (Box 97)
      - 1995, David Sklaver (WRG President) and Tom Fagan (CFO) articles (embezzlement case) (Box 97)
      - 1995, General (Box 97)
    - Clippings (continued) (Box 98)
      - 1995, General (Box 98)
    - Clippings (continued) (Box 99)
      - 1995-1997, General (Box 99)
    - Clippings (continued) (Box 100)
      - 1997-1998, General (Box 100)
    - Newsletter files, undated (Box 100)
    - Newsletters
      - Ad Lib, originals, 1993-1994 (Box 100)
      - All is Wells, originals, 1994-1997 (Box 100)
    - Memos to staff, 1993-1997 (Box 101)
    - Press releases, 1986-1989 (Box 101)
    - Personnel releases, 1990-1994 (Box 101)
    - Press releases, 1991-1992 (Box 101)
    - Press releases, 1993-1997 (Box 102)
    - WRG-BDDP press conference, 1996 (Box 102)
    - Ad Council
      - General press, 1993-1994 (Box 102)
      - Domestic violence, 1994 (Box 102)
      - Drunk driving, 1993 (Box 102)
      - Drunk driving press kits, 1993-1994 (Box 103)
      - Drunk driving, miscellaneous, 1993-1994 (Box 103)
    - Disruption
      - General files, 1996-1997 (Box 103)
      - Book, Disruption: Overturning Conventions and Shaking Up the Marketplace, 1996 (Box 103)
      - Brochures, 1992 (Box 103)
      - Clippings, 1990-1996 (Box 103)
      - Handbook, circa 1996 (Box 103)
      - Handbook (continued), circa 1996 (Box 104)
      - Presentations
        - Untitled, 1991 (Box 104)
        - Challenging Conventional Wisdom, 1991 (Box 104)
        - Practicing Disruption, 2 copies, undated (Box 104)
      - Press releases, undated (Box 104)
      - Promotional materials, 1997 (Box 104)
    - Tome 1--BDDP: Les Dix Premières Années, 1984-1993, 2 copies, circa 1994 (Box 104)
- Audiovisual Materials, 1954-1998 and undated (Acc. 98-0396), 140 boxes
  Scope and Contents note
  Restrictions on access: Audiovisual materials are closed to researchers until use copies can be made. Contact Research Services for more information.
  - Video and Film
    - Akadama Wine (Box 1)
      - 1. Akadama Wine. Undated. TRT: :40 (Box 1)
    - Aldi Inc.
      - 1. Aldi Bread. 1980. TRT: :30 (Box 1)
      - 2. Aldi Bread. 1979. TRT: :30 (Box 1)
      - 3. Aldi Bread. 1980. TRT: :30 (Box 1)
    - Alka Seltzer (Miles Labs)
      - AS Plus Pre-WRG, 1966-1970 Advertising--16 spots (list inside) 1975. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 1)
      - AS 54. Allergend That's Why They Call it Allergend. 1986. TRT: 1:00 (Box 1)
      - AS 64. Can't Find It, Testimonial. 1980. TRT: 1:00 (Box 1)
      - AS 70. Somewhere in America, Somewhere in America Relief, Somewhere in America Mood,. 1981. TRT: 2:00 (Box 1)
      - AS 76. The Longest Walk, America's Home Remedy Waits. 1982. TRT: 1:00 (Box 1)
      - AS 91. Historical Reel. 1976. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 1)
      - AS Plus. Master Reel (Old Book). 1979. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 1)
      - ASP 11. Buffalo Cole Testimonials III Revised. 1978. TRT: :30 (Box 1)
      - ASP 12. Alka Seltzer Plus--Historical--Breakfast in Bed. Undated. TRT: :30 (Box 1)
      - ASP 27. America/Flu. 1980. TRT: :30 (Box 1)
      - ASP 28. Alka Seltzer Plus. Undated. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 1)
    - Alka Seltzer (Miles Labs) (continued) (Box 2)
      - ASP 29. Cold Medicine--Pittsburgh Cold, St. Louis Cold. 1980. TRT: 1:00 (Box 2)
      - ASP 40. NY Colds, Tough Cities (No Slates Rev). 1982. TRT: 1:00 (Box 2)
      - ASP 41. Capsule/Tablets. 1983. TRT: :30 (Box 2)
      - ASP 42. Winter-Harbor alt. 1983. TRT: :30 (Box 2)
      - ASP 43. American Flu Revised. 1984. TRT: :30 (Box 2)
      - ASP 44. New England Cold Rev., Winter Harbor Rev. 1983. TRT: 1:00 (Box 2)
      - AST 45. Alka Seltzer Plus Winter Harbor Rev. (Bars & Slates) -- Master. 1984. TRT: :30 (Box 2)
      - ASP 46. Plus Cold Medicine Small Town Celebrities--Dairy Farmer. 1984. TRT: :30 (Box 2)
      - ASP 47. Plus Cold Medicine Winter Harbor Rev. 2 Master. 1984. TRT: :30 (Box 2)
      - ASP 48. More Pain Relief (Non Air Test). Circa 1984. TRT: :30 (Box 2)
      - ASP 49. Plus More Pain Relief Rev. I (Non Air Test). Circa 1984. TRT: :30 (Box 2)
      - ASP 50. Plus More Pain Relief Rev. II (Non Air Test). 1985. TRT: :30 (Box 2)
      - ASP 51. Plus Trucker, Firefighters. 1985. TRT: 1:00 (Box 2)
      - ASP 52. Allergend Clown. 1985. TRT: :30 (Box 2)
      - ASP 53. Plus Cold Medicine Trucker, Firefighters. 1985. TRT: :30 (Box 2)
      - ASP 55. School Bus Driver, Green Gay, Green Bay. Circa 1986. TRT: 1:15 (Box 2)
    - Alka Seltzer (Miles Labs) (continued) (Box 3)
      - ASP 56. Sinus End--Super Rev. Circa 1986. TRT: :30 (Box 3)
      - ASP 57. Plus Night Cold Time Medicine--3 spots. Circa 1986. TRT: 1:30 (Box 3)
      - ASP 58. Plus Night Time Cold Medicine Joe Wilson. Circa 1986. TRT: :30 (Box 3)
      - ASP 59. Plus Nighttime Medicine--2 spots. Circa 1986. TRT: 1:00 (Box 3)
      - ASP 60. Portland, Oregon. 1986. TRT: :30 (Box 3)
      - ASP 61. Plus 4 spots. 1986. TRT: 2:00 (Box 3)
      - ASP 62. Plus Nighttime Cold Medicine Portland-Oregon. 1986. TRT: :30 (Box 3)
      - ASP 63. Plus Nighttime Cold Medicine--2 spots. 1986. TRT: :45 (Box 3)
      - ASP 64. Plus Cold Medicine Cold of the Wild, Trawler. Circa 1986. TRT: 1:00 (Box 3)
      - ASP 65. ASP Nighttime-6 spots--ANIMATICS. Circa 1987. TRT: Circa 3:00 (Box 3)
      - AST 66. Plus--3 spots. Circa 1987. TRT: 1:15 (Box 3)
      - AST 67. Plus Nighttime Cold Medicine--1 good spot. Circa 1987. TRT: :15 (Box 3)
      - AST 68. Plus--5 spots. 1987. TRT: 2:30 (Box 3)
      - AST 69. Plus-Night Time Cold Medicine 1 good spot. 1987. TRT: :15 (Box 3)
      - AST 70. ASPCM--5 spots. 1987. TRT: 2:30 (Box 3)
      - AST 71. Plus--1 good spot. 1987. TRT: :30 (Box 3)
    - Alka Seltzer (Miles Labs) (continued) (Box 4)
      - AST 72. AS--2 Spots. 1987. TRT: 1:00 (Box 4)
      - AST 73. Plus Nighttime Cold Medicine 2 spots. 1988. TRT: :45 (Box 4)
      - AST 74. Plus Cold Medicine--2 spots. 1988. TRT: 1:00 (Box 4)
      - AST 75. Plus Cold Medicine--Vignettes. 1988. TRT: :15 (Box 4)
      - AST 76. Nighttime Cold Medicine--8 spots. 1988. TRT: 3:00 (Box 4)
      - ASP 77. Plus Nighttime--Vig/Blinking Box/Non-new. 1988. TRT: :30 (Box 4)
      - ASP 78. Plus Nighttime--2 spots. 1988. TRT: 1:00 (Box 4)
      - AST 79. Cold Plus--Trawler Tag Non-new. 1988. TRT: :30 (Box 4)
      - ASP 80. AS--2 spots. Circa 1988. TRT: :45 (Box 4)
      - AST 81. Plus Cold Medicine--2 spots. Circa 1989. TRT: 1:00 (Box 4)
      - AST 82. Plus Cold Medicine--Shopping Mall Mary. 1989. TRT: :30 (Box 4)
      - AST 83. Plus Cold Medicine--2 spots. 1989. TRT: :30 (Box 4)
      - ASP 84. Plus Cold Medicine--Shopping Mall Multiple. 1989. TRT: :30 (Box 4)
      - ASP 85. Plus--2 spots. 1989. TRT: 1:00 (Box 4)
      - AST 86. AS--8 spots. 1989. TRT: 3:30 (Box 4)
      - APT 87. Plus--2 spots. 1989. TRT: :30 (Box 4)
    - Alka Seltzer (Miles Labs) (continued) (Box 5)
      - AST 88. Plus--4 spots. 1989. TRT: 1:15 (Box 5)
      - AST 89. Plus--Happy Face. 1989. TRT: :30 (Box 5)
      - ASPlus 90. ASPCM--5 spots. 1989. TRT: 1:45 (Box 5)
      - ASPlus 91. Plus--Hi-Ho. 1989. TRT: :30 (Box 5)
      - ASPlus 92. Plus Cold Medicine. 1989. TRT: :30 (Box 5)
      - AST 93. Plus--Drink. 1989. TRT: :30 (Box 5)
      - AST 94. Plus Cold Medicine--Big Speedy. 1989. TRT: :30 (Box 5)
      - AST 95. Plus Healing Waters. 1989. TRT: :30 (Box 5)